Guide to the Hotel School video, film and tape collection, 1929-1993.
Hotel School video film collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hotel School video, film and tape collection, 1972-1993.
28-11-3951
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration.
17 cubic feet.
Videos
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes VHS, 3/4" and betamax tapes of Hotel Ezra Cornell (HEC) Events; Management Intern Program (MIP); Hotel School Courses; Hotel School Events, Development, History and films of Campus Scenes, the Meek Children and Company Films.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes VHS, 3/4" and betamax tapes of Hotel Ezra Cornell (HEC) Events; Management Intern Program (MIP); Hotel School Courses; Hotel School Events, Development, History and films of Campus Scenes, the Meek Children, and Company Films.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Meek, Howard B., 1893-.; Cornell University.; Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration -- Societies, etc.; Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration; Hotel Ezra Cornell.; Management Intern Program.
Subjects:
Hotel management schools -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.; Hotel management -- Study and teaching.; Hotel management schools; Hotel management -- Study and teaching; Societies
Places:
New York (State) -- Ithaca
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.; Motion pictures (visual works).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. School of Hotel Administration Courses
Boxes 1-7
Series II. School of Hotel Administration Events, Development, and History
Boxes 7-10
Series III. School of Hotel Administration Hotel Ezra Cornell (HEC) Events
Boxes 11-14
Series IV. School of Hotel Administration Management Intern Program (MIP)
Boxes 15-16
Series V. Films and Cassette Tapes
Boxes 17
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. School of Hotel Administration Courses
  - HA 430 Introduction 9/6/89, V-7603 (Box 1)
  - HA 542: BASKIN ROBBINS CASE STUDY (2/8/89), V-7604 (Box 1)
  - PRESIDENTS ROUNDTABLE CLASSROOM EDIT FOOTAGE (4-14-89), V-7605 (Box 1)
  - HA 436: FOODS & EATING CUSTOMS OF FIJI (10/13/88), V-7606 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: CLEARY, SARAH
  - HA 536: NUTRITION & FITNESS FOR HOTELS, SPAS & RESORTS (2/27/89), V-7607 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: CLUFF, SHEILA
  - HA 430: SPIRITS (3/8/89), V-7608 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: COE, DONALD
  - HA 450/651 (9/1/93), V-7609 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: Corgel
    Publisher: School of Hotel Administration, Cornell University / Ithaca, NY
  - HA 450/651 Make-up Lecture 2 (9/15/93), V-7610 (Box 1)
  - HA 405: LA QUINTA HOTELS (3/16/89), V-7611 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: DAVIS, DAVE
  - HA 436: ITALIAN, V-7612 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: DI BELARDINO, PHILIP
  - FOOD BANKING, V-7613 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: FEINBERG, BART
  - HA 535: FISHER & LEVY (3/28/89), V-7614 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: FISHER, CHARLES
  - HA 430: BEER (4/19/89), V-7615 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: GARLAND, PAT
  - HA 430: NEW YORK (2/8/89), V-7616 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: GOLDWYN, CRAIG
  - HA 430: New York State Wines (9/20/95), V-7617 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: Goldwyn, Craig
    Publisher: Cornell University School of Hotel Administration
  - HA 405: CONVENTION SERVICES (11/16/88), V-7618 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: HAVENS, ANN - GRAND HYATT
  - HA 135: CHEESE (3/3/89), V-7619 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: LANG, BARBARA
  - HA 430: CALIFORNIA (4/26/89), V-7620 (Box 1)
  - HA 430: FOOD & WINE (3/29/89), V-7621 (Box 1)
  - LECTURE (4/11/88), V-7622 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: MANDEL
  - HA 430 (4/12/89), V-7623 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: MONDAVI, ROBERT
  - HA 430: SPIRITS (4/5/89), V-7624 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: MULLER, CHRIS
  - HA 436: RISK & LIABILITY (3/29/89), V-7625 (Box 1)
  - HA 430: RESPONSIBLE DRINKING/VALUE WINES (3/15/89), V-7626 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: MULLER, CHRIS/MUTKOSKI
  - HA 430: Champagne (12/6/95), V-7627 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: MUTKOSKI
  - HA 430: CHAMPAGNE (5/3/89), V-7628 (Box 1)
  - HA 430: COMPONENTS (2/1/89), V-7629 (Box 1)
  - HA 430: FRENCH (2/15/89), V-7630 (Box 1)
  - HA 430: INTRODUCTION (1/25/89), V-7631 (Box 1)
  - HA 430: Introduction (9/6/95), V-7632 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: Mutkoski, Steve
    Publisher: Cornell University School of Administration
  - HA 430: Value Wines (11/8/95), V-7633 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: Nash, Abby
  - HA 522, PROF. ARBEL, 11/16/89, V-7634 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: ORKIN, ERIC B.
  - HA 252/222/452: LAVENTHOL & HORWATH (3/31/86), V-7635 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: PATERSON, BOB
  - HA 405: SVP MARKETING (4/19/89), V-7636 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: RICHARDS, JOHN
  - HA 536/338: GLOBAL BRAIN, V-7637 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: RUSSELL, PETER
  - HA 405: EVP OPERATIONS (4/12/89), V-7638 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: SHARPE, JOHN
  - HA 430: ITALIAN (3/1/89), V-7639 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: SORRE, LUCIO
  - HA 436: BURGUNDY (3/1/89), V-7640 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: WESSON, JOSHUA
  - HA 536: SPA & WELLNESS (3/1/89), V-7641 (Box 1)
    Speaker/Producer: ZIMMER, ROBERT
  - HA 536: WELLNESS (2/28/89), V-7642 (Box 1)
  - SPA & WELLNESS (3/1/89), V-7643 (Box 1)
  - ALMANAC II, SPRING 1982, V-7644 (Box 2)
  - HA 430: CALIFORNIA WINES 1/10/85, V-7645 (Box 2)
  - HA 430: COOL WHITE WINES OF GERMANY 1/9/85, V-7646 (Box 2)
  - LAMB: SELECTION, PROCUREMENT & SUPPLY, V-7647 (Box 2)
    HA 435
  - TABLE SERVICE TIPS, V-7648 (Box 2)
    FOOD & BEVERAGE 6/26/85
  - VEAL & PORK: SELECTION, PROCUREMENT & SUPPLY, V-7649 (Box 2)
  - SEMINAR W/SHA UNDERGRADS 2/7/86, V-7650 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: BLANCHARD, KEN
  - HA 323/723: GUEST LECTURE (11/3/?), V-7651 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: DESMONDS, JOHN
  - SPECIAL LECTURE (10/20/84), V-7652 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: MATT, F.X.
  - IDENTIFICATION & UTILIZATION OF BEEF CUTS (9/85), V-7653 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: NORKUS, GREG
    Publisher: SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION, CORNELL UNIVERSITY / STATLER HALL
  - HA 354 (4/22/86), V-7654 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: REDLIN
  - WHY MARKETING? (3 copies), V-7655, V-7656, V-7657 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: RENAGHAN, LEO
  - HA 541: GUEST SPEAKER, D. DIVI HOTELS, V-7658 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: SLATER
  - LECTURES, V-7659 (Box 2)
    Speaker/Producer: WASMUTH, DAVIS & EYSTER
  - HA 102: ARA 9/25/87, Betacam V-7660 (Box 3)
    #1
  - HA 402: ARA 9/25/87 (HA 102 last 5:00), Betacam V-7661 (Box 3)
  - HA 135: OWNING A RESTAURANT (11/11/88) (2 copies), VHS V-7662, V-7663 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: BASTIANICK, LIDIA
  - FLORENCE BERGER, 10/3/85, VHS V-7664 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: BERGER, FLORENCE
  - HA 102 #2: REGENT INTERNATIONAL HOTELS, 11/6/87, Betacam V-7665 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: BURNS, ROBERT, PRESIDENT
  - HA 102 #3: REGENT INTERNATIONAL HOTELS, 11/6/87, Betacam V-7666 (Box 3)
  - HA 102 TAPE #1 & #2 10/21/88, Betacam V-7667, V-7668 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: C.T. MOTTEK
    Publisher: CORNELL UNIVERSITY
  - HA 402 TAPE #1 & #2 10/21/88, Betacam V-7669, V-7670 (Box 3)
  - MARKETING PRESENTATION 5/5/78, VHS V-7671 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: CHRISTIAN, PROF.
  - HA 430: BEER (Also Labeled "Wines") 9-26-90, VHS V-7672 (Box 3)
  - GARNISHING WITH FOOD 7/75, VHS V-7673 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: HERMAN, PROF.
  - OFFSHORE RESORT PROPERTIES, 3/5/72, VHS V-7674 (Box 3)
    PART 1 OF 2
    Speaker/Producer: HOLTZMAN, MR.; PRESIDENT OF ROCKRESORTS
  - FOOD & WINE 10/11/89 (2 copies), VHS V-7675, V-7676 (Box 3)
  - ANHEISER BUSCH 4/27/88, Betacam V-7677, V-7678, V-7679 (Box 3)
    Tapes II, III, and IV
  - FROZEN FOOD PURCHASING, 2/77, VHS V-7680 (Box 3)
  - HA 430, CHAMPAGNE, 12/6/89, VHS V-7681 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: MUTKOSKI, STEVE
  - TOURISM SEMINAR, 5/74, VHS V-7682 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: NODEN, MAC
  - TOURISM SEMINAR, 5/74, VHS V-7683 (Box 3)
    PART 2 OF 2
  - HA 402: SINGLE ROOM OCCUPANCY HOUSING CORP. 10/7/88, Betacam V-7684 (Box 3)
    TAPE 3 of 4
    Speaker/Producer: RAUBESON, ANDREW
  - HA 402 #2, 10/23/87, Betacam V-7685 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: SEAGRAM
  - EDP IN THE LEISURE TIME INDUSTRIES; SPONSOR: PROF. MOORE, 5/3/76, VHS V-7686 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: SEIBURGH, JULES
  - FRANCHISING 10/76, VHS V-7687 (Box 3)
    1 OF 2
    Speaker/Producer: SHERRY
  - HA 741 11/16/89 (2 copies), VHS V-7688, V-7689 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: SHIFFLET, DOUG
  - HA 402-1, 11/18/88, Betacam V-7690 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: SMALL, BOB
  - HA 402-2, 11/18/88, Betacam V-7691 (Box 3)
  - HA 402-3, 11/18/88, Betacam V-7692 (Box 3)
  - MITCH SNYDER, 11/30/88, Betacam V-7693 (Box 3)
    TAPE #1
    Speaker/Producer: SNYDER, MITCH
  - MITCH SNYDER 2, 11/30/88, Betacam V-7694 (Box 3)
  - MITCH SNYDER PRESS CONFERENCE, 11/30/88, Betacam V-7695 (Box 3)
  - WIXT PRODUCTION, 7/8/86, VHS V-7696 (Box 3)
    Speaker/Producer: TABACCHI, MARY
  - HA 402 TAPE #1 11/13/87, Betacam V-7697 (Box 3)
    ASTON
    Speaker/Producer: TATIBOUET
    Publisher: CORNELL UNIVERSITY / A103
  - FACULTY SEMINAR, IMPACT OF ENERGY CRISIS ON HOSP. IND., 12/10/73, VHS V-7698 (Box 4)
    PART 2 12/10/73
  - HA 430: VALUE WINES (11-7-90), VHS V-7699 (Box 4)
  - HA 430: WINES OF CALIFORNIA, OREGON, & WASHINGTON, VHS V-7700 (Box 4)
    10/17/1990
  - HA 430: WINES OF CALIFORNIA, VOLUMES III & IV, VHS V-7701 (Box 4)
  - TABLESIDE 1 4/3/85, VHS V-7702 (Box 4)
  - TABLESIDE 2 4/3/85, VHS V-7703 (Box 4)
  - FLORENCE BERGER, 10/7/85, U-matic V-7704 (Box 4)
    TAPE 1
  - FLORENCE BERGER, 10/7/85, U-matic V-7705 (Box 4)
    TAPE 2
  - HA 402 #1, REGENT INTERNATIONAL HOTELS, 11/6/87, Betacam V-7706 (Box 4)
  - HA 323/722, BALLY OF NEW JERSEY, 11/13/78 CASINO FINANCING, U-matic V-7707 (Box 4)
    Speaker/Producer: CALLNIN, WILLIAM
  - HA 265, INTRO SPEECHES IN CLASS, 1/30/85, VHS V-7708 (Box 4)
    Speaker/Producer: HERMAN
  - DICK HOLTZMAN 4, 9/17/85, U-matic V-7709 (Box 4)
    TAPE 4
    Speaker/Producer: HOLTZMAN, DICK
  - JJC, 9/17/85 [JOHN J. CLARK], U-matic V-7710 (Box 4)
    TAPE 3
  - 2/22/1984, VHS V-7711 (Box 4)
    Speaker/Producer: LAKOSH, RUDOLPH
  - HA 430: INTRO TO WINES 1-23-91, VHS V-7712 (Box 4)
  - HOSP SYST. ROOM 10/17/85, U-matic V-7713 (Box 4)
    Speaker/Producer: MOORE, DICK
  - HA 430, INTRODUCTION, 1/24/90, VHS V-7714 (Box 4)
  - FISH (11-10-80), VHS V-7715 (Box 4)
  - HA 402, SINGLE ROOM OCCUPANCY HOUSING CORP. 10/7/88, Betacam V-7716 (Box 4)
  - LEO RENAGHAN - 3/8/84, VHS V-7717 (Box 4)
  - MARKETING II, 6/28/84, VHS V-7718 (Box 4)
  - GOOD MORNING SHERATON, VHS V-7719, V-7720 (Box 4)
    2 TAPES: PART I & II
    Speaker/Producer: SHERATON
  - MITCH SNYDER, 11/30/88, Betacam V-7721 (Box 4)
    TAPE #3
  - HA 430: ITALIAN WINES (10-24-90), VHS V-7722 (Box 4)
  - HA 102 -#2 11/13/87, Betacam V-7723 (Box 4)
  - WELCOME TO WYATT'S -- A WINNING COMBINATION (6/25/87), VHS V-7724 (Box 4)
    Speaker/Producer: WYATT'S
  - HA 102 #1, THE GEORGE LANG CORP., 9/18/87, Betacam V-7725 (Box 4)
    Speaker/Producer: YOUNG, ANDREW J.
  - HA 102 #2, THE GEORGE LANG CORP., 9/18/87, Betacam V-7726 (Box 4)
  - HA 402 #2, 9/18/87, Betacam V-7727 (Box 4)
  - FACULTY SEMINAR: IMPACT OF ENERGY CRISIS 12/10/73, VHS V-7728 (Box 5)
  - HA 103 12/5/89, VHS V-7729 (Box 5)
  - HA 405/HA 705: U.S. LODGING DISCUSSION (3/8/90), VHS V-7730 (Box 5)
  - HA 430 GERMAN WINES/ALSACE 4/4/90, VHS V-7731 (Box 5)
  - HA 522 10/26/89, VHS V-7732, V-7733 (Box 5)
    APPROACH TO NEW MANAGEMENT (2 copies)
    Speaker/Producer: BROOKS, RICHARD
  - FISHER 1, 5/2/84, VHS V-7734 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: DERMODY
  - HA 522, PROF. ARBEL, 11/9/89, VHS V-7735 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: ELKINS, STEVEN
  - HA 103 11/16/89, VHS V-7736 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: FITZGERALD, MIKE
  - HA 430 11/29/89, VHS V-7737 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: GARLAND
  - HA 430 2/7/90, VHS V-7738 (Box 5)
    NY STATE WINES
  - HA 430 5/2/90, VHS V-7739 (Box 5)
    SPARKLING WINES
    Speaker/Producer: GOURDIN, ROBERT
  - HA 430 11/15/89, VHS V-7740 (Box 5)
    CALIFORNIA
    Speaker/Producer: LANG
  - HA 430 10/4/89, VHS V-7741 (Box 5)
    LOIRE
  - HA 430 CALIFORNIA WINES (3/14/90), VHS V-7742 (Box 5)
  - HA 430, FOOD & WINE 3/28/90, VHS V-7743 (Box 5)
  - HA 436: FOOD & WINE TASTING 11/23/88, VHS V-7744 (Box 5)
  - INGLENOOK VINEYARDS, 3/21/85, VHS V-7745 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: LANG, BARBARA & STEVE MUTKOSKI
  - NODEN AIRLINE MANAGEMENT, 3/10/88, Betacam V-7746 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: LUNDBERG, CRAIG
  - NODEN AIRLINE MANAGEMENT, 3/10/88, Betacam V-7747 (Box 5)
  - EYP 86, VHS V-7748 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: MARIANI
  - HA 430 9/27/89, VHS V-7749 (Box 5)
    FRENCH
    Speaker/Producer: MILLIGAN, DAVID
  - RESORT FINAL PROJECT (SPEECHES) 5/9/77, VHS V-7750, V-7751 (Box 5)
    TWO TAPES: PART 3 OF 3 AND PART 1 OF 3
    Speaker/Producer: MPS STUDENTS
  - HA 430 10/18/89, VHS V-7752 (Box 5)
    RESPONSIBLE DRINKING
  - HA 430 2/14/90, VHS V-7753 (Box 5)
  - HA 430 2/21/90, VHS V-7754 (Box 5)
    LOIRE VALLEY
  - HA 430 3/7/90, VHS V-7755 (Box 5)
  - HA 430 4/18/90, VHS V-7756 (Box 5)
    VALUE WINES
  - HA 430 9/13/89, VHS V-7757 (Box 5)
    COMPONENTS
  - HA 430 2/28/90, VHS V-7758 (Box 5)
    ITALY
  - HA 338 3/5/90, VHS V-7759 (Box 5)
    Speaker/Producer: TABACCHI
  - HA 436 4/11/90, VHS V-7760 (Box 5)
    SEAGRAM WINES
    Speaker/Producer: BELLUS, BOB
  - CASES IN DISCIPLINE & DISCHARGE, U-matic V-7761 (Box 6)
  - HENNESSY, U-matic V-7762 (Box 6)
  - MARRIOTT SPIRIT OF SUCCESS, U-matic V-7763 (Box 6)
    BUENA VISTA PALACE
  - PATTERN FOR INSTRUCTION 4 STEPS, U-matic V-7764 (Box 6)
  - VILLA BANFI - "THE GRAND TOUR" (6/5/85), U-matic V-7765 (Box 6)
  - BOCA RATON HOTEL - J. FERRER & BACK OF THE HOUSE, U-matic V-7766 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: ADMINISTRATION
  - BEACON HOTEL CORPORATION (1990), U-matic V-7767 (Box 6)
    YOU GOT WHAT IT TAKES
    Speaker/Producer: BEACON HOTEL CORPORATION
    Publisher: BEACON HOTEL CORPORATION
  - DUNFEY HOTELS, U-matic V-7768 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: CANAS, JOHN
  - CNN INTERVIEW (10/6/85) MONTALANO - "THE GRAND TOUR", U-matic V-7769 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: MARIANNI, JOHN
  - TODAY'S INN THING, U-matic V-7770 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: MOTROVOLA/HOLIDAY INN
  - CUTTING AND WRAPPING MEAT AND FISH, U-matic V-7771 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION
  - VILLA BANFI (10/22/82), U-matic V-7772 (Box 6)
  - VILLA BANFI, (10/24/79), PART 2, U-matic V-7773 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: SORRE, LUCIO M.
  - VILLA BANFI WINES (10/24/79) PART 1, U-matic V-7774 (Box 6)
  - DIRECTOR OF MARKETING & SALES (3/17/87), U-matic V-7775 (Box 6)
    Speaker/Producer: WIGGINS, SCOTT
  - HA 265 SECOND ROUND, U-matic V-7776 (Box 7)
    TAPE #8
  - HA 765: PROJECTS, U-matic V-7777 (Box 7)
  - ALMANAC IV, VHS V-7778 (Box 7)
    Speaker/Producer: ENDERS, FRAN & ROY ALVAREZ
  - UNDERGRADUATE SEMINAR / HATFIELD ADDRESS (11/5/86), VHS V-7779 (Box 7)
    Speaker/Producer: FERRIS, RICHARD
  - HOW TO USE THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE: MURDER IN THE CATHEDRAL (8/27/75), VHS V-7780 (Box 7)
    SPONSOR: MS. HERMAN
    Speaker/Producer: HERMAN, MS.
  - ROCKRESORTS INTERVIEW, NYC, 7/31/86, VHS V-7781 (Box 7)
    Speaker/Producer: HOLTZMAN, RICHARD
  - NODEN AIRLINE MANAGEMENT 3/8/88, VHS V-7782 (Box 7)
    Speaker/Producer: KAHN, ALFRED
  - HOUSTON CLUB 10/6/77, VHS V-7783 (Box 7)
    Speaker/Producer: WATTS, RAY
- Series II. School of Hotel Administration Events, Development, and History
  - Cornell University School of Hotel Administration Commencement, Class of 2005 (May 29,2005), VHS V-7784 (Box 7)
  - Cornell University Senior Convocation (May 29, 2004), VHS V-7785 (Box 7)
  - School of Hotel Administration Class of 2004 (May 30, 2004), VHS V-7786 (Box 7)
  - School of Hotel Administration Diploma Ceremony, VHS V-7787 (Box 7)
    SHA Commencement 2002
  - School of Hotel Administration Diploma Ceremony (May 25, 2003), VHS V-7788 (Box 7)
    SHA Commencement 2003
  - A Farewell to Roy Alvarez and Florence Berger, Wednesday, May 12, 2004, Carrier Ballroom, Statler Hotel, VHS V-7789 (Box 7)
    Speaker/Producer: School of Hotel Administration
  - It's Yours at the Statler Hotel (circa 1989?), VHS V-7790 (Box 7)
  - The Teaching Hotel "Reaching Higher" (circa 1996?), VHS V-7791 (Box 7)
  - CASE OF ABBY'S RESTAURANT, 8/19/87 (2 copies), VHS V-7792, U-matic V-7793 (Box 8)
  - CHINA TRIP, U-matic V-7794 (Box 8)
  - DEAN 1, 11/6/84, U-matic V-7795 (Box 8)
  - DEAN 2; CLASSROOM 335; IBM ROOM, 11/9/84, U-matic V-7796 (Box 8)
  - DOLLY SHOTS OUTSIDE OF SCHOOL & URIS, U-matic V-7797 (Box 8)
  - EXP DINNER (4/12/85) [Two copies: Tape 1 and Tape 2], U-matic V-7798, V-7799 (Box 8)
  - GROUNDBREAKING CEREMONY SHA 10/17/86, U-matic V-7800 (Box 8)
  - JJC-CPD, 3/3/87 [JOHN J. CLARK], U-matic V-7801 (Box 8)
  - SHA DEVELOPMENT, U-matic V-7802 (Box 8)
  - WALDORF ASTORIA 50TH ANNIVERSARY, U-matic V-7803 (Box 8)
  - INTERVIEW, 4/30/82; COMPUTER ROOM; ALMANAC III, U-matic V-7804 (Box 8)
    Speaker/Producer: BADER et al
  - JJC DEVELOPMENT, 10/24/85 [JOHN J. CLARK], U-matic V-7805 (Box 8)
    Speaker/Producer: DEAN CLARK
  - MORE MEEK 11/16/83, U-matic V-7806 (Box 8)
    Speaker/Producer: MEEK
  - CENTER FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, U-matic V-7807 (Box 8)
    Speaker/Producer: SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMIN. CU
  - ALMANAC I, U-matic V-7808 (Box 8)
    Speaker/Producer: SHA
  - ALUMNI UPDATE OF STATLER RENOVATION, SPRING/SUMMER 1987, VHS V-7809 (Box 9)
  - CAREER DAY FOOTAGE WITH GRAPHICS, VHS V-7810 (Box 9)
    10/23/1987
  - CENTER FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, VHS V-7811 (Box 9)
    THE SHA CORNELL UNIVERSITY
  - CORNELL UNIVERSITY SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION, VHS V-7812 (Box 9)
    Publisher: CORNELL UNIVERSITY / ITHACA, NY
  - HOTEL CONSTRUCTION, VHS V-7813 (Box 9)
    TAPE 28-34
  - HOTEL CONSTRUCTION, VHS V-7814 (Box 9)
    TAPE 35
  - HOTEL CONSTRUCTION, VHS V-7815 (Box 9)
    TAPE 36-40
  - HOTEL DEVELOPMENT, 8/86, VHS V-7816 (Box 9)
  - HOTEL REUNION #1, 5/19/87, VHS V-7817 (Box 9)
  - HOTEL REUNION #2, 5/19/87, VHS V-7818 (Box 9)
  - JJC [JOHN J. CLARK], VHS V-7819 (Box 9)
  - MPS 88 SLIDE SHOW, Betacam V-7937 (Box 9)
  - MPS MEMORIES 1988 (2 copies), VHS V-7820, V-7821 (Box 9)
  - ROUGH EDIT - A TOUR OF THE SCHOOL 3/1/88, VHS V-7822 (Box 9)
  - SHA CONSTRUCTION UPDATE, 3/21/88, VHS V-7823 (Box 9)
  - SHA GROUNDBREAKING (10/17/86), VHS V-7824 (Box 9)
  - STATLER HALL 1949, VHS V-7825 (Box 9)
  - STATLER HALL ALUMNI BUILDING UPDATE, SUMMER 1987, VHS V-7826 (Box 9)
  - STATE OF THE SCHOOL ADDRESS, 10/2/79, VHS V-7827 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: BECK, DEAN ROBERT A.
  - CANDID COMMENTS W/ CLARK & COMPANY 12/2/88, VHS V-7828 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: CLARK & COMPANY
  - DEAN CLARK, 5/14/87, Betacam V-7829 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: CLARK, DEAN
  - DEAN CLARK, 5/14/87, Betacam V-7830 (Box 9)
  - DEAN CLARK INTERVIEW, VHS V-7831 (Box 9)
  - DEVELOPMENT, 10/24/85, VHS V-7832 (Box 9)
  - STATE OF THE SCHOOL ADDRESS 1982, VHS V-7833 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: CLARK (DEAN)
  - STUDENT BODY FORUM (11/8/88), VHS V-7834 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: CORNELL HOTEL SCHOOL
  - THREE PROFS AND DEAN, VHS V-7835 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: DEAN AND THREE PROFS
  - HOLTZMAN, NYC, 7/31/86, VHS V-7836 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: HOLTZMAN
  - HOTEL DEVELOPMENT #5, VHS V-7837 (Box 9)
    2/6/1987
  - NEW ORGANIZATIONAL STRUCT. FOR EFFECTIVE SERV. DEL. IN HOTELS, VHS V-7838 (Box 9)
    11/10/1988
    Speaker/Producer: KAY, MICHAEL
  - MPS PRESENTATION 4/19/84, VHS V-7839 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: NAPLES, KHEEL, AND LEMAN
  - TRAVEL INTERVIEW, WICB-TV, 4/23/86, VHS V-7840 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: NODEN
  - DEVELOPMENT WORK TAPE, 3/25/86, VHS V-7841 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: RHODES & HOLTZMAN
  - MPS DIPLOMA CEREMONY 1993 (2 copies), VHS V-7842, V-7843 (Box 9)
    Publisher: SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION / CORNELL UNIVERSITY, STATLER HALL
  - STOUFFERS HOTEL PLACEMENT, VHS V-7844 (Box 9)
    Speaker/Producer: SHA: RUDY LAKOSH, SPEAKER
  - BINENKORB CENTER CONSTRUCTION, 7/19/84, VHS V-7845 (Box 10)
  - CAMPAIGN COMMITTEE 1, 4/16/86, VHS V-7846 (Box 10)
  - DEVELOPMENT WALDORF, BLANCHARD, MARRIOTT, 5/86 (2 tapes), VHS V-7847, V-7848 (Box 10)
  - GRADUATION 1985, VHS V-7849 (Box 10)
  - GRADUATION 1986, VHS V-7850 (Box 10)
  - HOTEL DEMOLITION 11/3-4/86, U-matic V-7851 (Box 10)
  - HOTEL DEVELOPMENT, 12/86, VHS V-7852 (Box 10)
  - MPS SLIDE SHOW 1988, VHS V-7853 (Box 10)
    TAKE 1
  - MPS SLIDE SHOW 1988, Betacam V-7854 (Box 10)
    TAKE 3
  - NARRATION BINENKORB CENTER, VHS V-7855 (Box 10)
  - OLD-NEW STATLER, 11/7/83, VHS V-7856 (Box 10)
  - REUNION UPDATE 6/12/87, VHS V-7857 (Box 10)
  - STATLER HALL ALUMNI BUILDING UPDATE, SUMMER 1987, VHS V-7858 (Box 10)
  - STATLER MODEL 5/15/87, Betacam V-7859 (Box 10)
  - STATE OF THE SCHOOL ADDRESS 3/13/81, VHS V-7860 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: BECK
  - ADDRESS TO ALUMNI AND FRIENDS - 3/4/79, VHS V-7861 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: BECK, DEAN
  - ODD FELLOWS HOME 7/31/81, VHS V-7862 (Box 10)
  - SCHOOL UPDATE, VHS V-7863 (Box 10)
  - CANDIDATE FOR DEAN, 2/17/81, VHS V-7864 (Box 10)
  - STATE OF THE SCHOOL, 10/24/83, VHS V-7865 (Box 10)
  - STATE OF THE SCHOOL, 4/15/83, VHS V-7866 (Box 10)
  - STATE OF THE SCHOOL ADDRESS, 9/27/85, VHS V-7867 (Box 10)
  - CANDID COMMENTS WITH CLARK & COMPANY 12/2/88, VHS V-7868 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: CLARK et al
  - CPD SPEECHES, VHS V-7869 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: CPD
  - KEITHAN INTERVIEW, VHS V-7870 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: KEITHAN
  - ALMANAC III, U-matic V-7871 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: LIZ, DICK, TRON
  - RENOVATION UPDATE, 4/8/86, VHS V-7872 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: PENNER, DICK
  - HOTEL DEVELOPMENT, 9/10/86, VHS V-7873 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: ROUGH, #3
  - A WALK THROUGH THE SCHOOL '88, VHS V-7874 (Box 10)
    HOTEL SHOW
    Publisher: SCHOOL OF HOTEL ADMINISTRATION
  - CAREER FAIR HOTEL SCHOOL, U-matic V-7875 (Box 10)
  - FOUR TALKS; TWO MILLION ROOMS; SPRING IN ITHACA, VHS V-7876 (Box 10)
    Speaker/Producer: STATLER, E.M.
- Series III. School of Hotel Administration Hotel Ezra Cornell (HEC) Events
  - HEC 56 RALLY SHOW, 4/29/81, U-matic V-7877 (Box 11)
  - TAPE 2 - LATE AFTERNOON TIL OPENING, U-matic V-7878 (Box 11)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 56
  - BACK OF HOUSE, U-matic V-7879 (Box 11)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 58
  - GATSBY'S GARAGE, CORNER CAFE, U-matic V-7880 (Box 11)
  - II - CORNER CAFE, CAVEMEN, BANQUET MEETING, U-matic V-7881 (Box 11)
  - PREP - FISH, FLOWERS, U-matic V-7882 (Box 11)
  - RALLY, OLIVER WIGGINS, U-matic V-7883 (Box 11)
  - STROLL IN THE PARK, U-matic V-7884 (Box 11)
  - THEO I, U-matic V-7885 (Box 11)
  - V, U-matic V-7886 (Box 11)
  - V - PIRATES AWAKENING, PREMIERE, U-matic V-7887 (Box 11)
  - VI, U-matic V-7888 (Box 11)
  - VII - BEV RM, THEE OUTSIDE, FLOWER SALAD, PIRATES, U-matic V-7889 (Box 11)
  - XI - AWAKEN DINNER SPEAKERS, BILL GRACE, U-matic V-7890 (Box 11)
  - BANQUET, U-matic V-7891 (Box 11)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 59
  - SPEECHES/BANQUET (4/27/85), U-matic V-7892 (Box 11)
    Speaker/Producer: HEC 60
  - GATSBY CORNER CAFE 10/28/83, VHS V-7893 (Box 12)
    HEC 58 MAIN DINING ROOM
  - HEC 1979 RALLY (UPPER CAMERA), U-matic V-7894 (Box 12)
  - HEC #2, 4/25/87, VHS V-7895 (Box 12)
  - HEC 53 RALLY REHEARSAL, 4/26/78, VHS V-7896 (Box 12)
  - HEC 55 RALLY SHOW, U-matic V-7897 (Box 12)
  - HEC 56 INKWELL, U-matic V-7898 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58, VHS V-7899 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58, 1983, VHS V-7900 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58 4/22 #1, VHS V-7901 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58 DESIGNING AND BUILDING OF EQUIPMENT 4/16/83, VHS V-7902 (Box 12)
  - HEC 58 THEO #2 & CHAMPAGNE, VHS V-7903 (Box 12)
  - HEC 59 PRE-WEEKEND #1, U-matic V-7904 (Box 12)
  - HEC '59, PRE-WEEKEND 4, U-matic V-7905 (Box 12)
  - HEC 59 WEEKEND #5, U-matic V-7906 (Box 12)
  - HEC 60, VHS V-7907 (Box 12)
    SEMINAR BREAKOUT 4/27/85
  - HEC 60 BALL GAME, VHS V-7908 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61, 4/18/86, VHS V-7909 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61, 4/18/86, VHS V-7910 (Box 12)
  - HEC 61, 4/18/86, VHS V-7911 (Box 12)